We continue to complete the production of the entire Wulong project.
After creating the bearded version, we need to create the bearded material.
I created some beards using XGen in Maya.
I will use the top focal angle to render in RNode with a 4K square resolution.
Back to Marvelous Designer, in order to make the material easy to use, we need to line up the UV first.
We recommend that you line up the UV pieces in Marvelous Designer, because 2D panels can also be used to line up the UV.
In order to maintain the structure of the face, it is easy to differentiate.
For these panels that form the face, I manually place them in a square area.
Select the UV panels that have been lined up, and place them in the 01 UV panel.
Select the remaining UV panels in the headboard, and select the Auto-Fill UV function to fill them into the UV panel in U1V0.
For the bearded version, since I created five types of beards, I will use the length to separate these UV panels, and place them in the same length.
Divide these UV panels into five groups.
Place the bearded material on the bearded material, and set the texture setting to Unified.
Then set the texture angle to 0.
Replace the hair line sticker, and then set the intensity of the hair line sticker.
Select multiple UV panels in a whole group, and then shrink them to the size of the bearded sticker.
You can observe the texture of the beard in the 3D window to confirm the texture effect.
For the dragon's head, I used Maya for modeling, and imported it in the OBJ format.
Choose Add for the loading type, and choose Add for the object type.
Click on the location bar in the upper right corner.
Then paste the dragon's head to the panel, and adjust the rotation position.
Do the same for the other dragon's head.
Select these two dragon's heads, change the color to red, and change the material type to silk.
Let's take a look at the effect of pasting the accessories to the material.
Open the simulation and drag the nose panel.
As the panel is adjusted, the accessories pasted on it will also move along with it.
So when recording animation, the effect of the animation will naturally be changed.
Next, let's make the line effect.
Select the line tool group, and open the line window.
Use the free line tool to double-click on the straight line on the outline of the film,
and add a line to the outline of the eyebrow film.
Marvelous Designer has six different line types.
I will choose the Overlock preset, and then increase the strength in the information,
the width in the specifications, the length, and the thickness of the line, and modify the color.
You can go to the Connect store to download more line types,
or define your own OBJ file as a line type.
For the line in the eye area, I will use the Diamond Satin style downloaded from Connect,
and then modify the corresponding properties.
Change the color to gold, and the material type to silk.
The nose part uses the same line as the eyebrow version.
Next, apply the Rise line downloaded from the Connect store to the inner line on the lip version,
and modify the corresponding properties according to your needs.
Select the side eyebrow version, and create an inner line using the Inner Line tool.
Remember to select the Extend inner line option.
You can choose the color as you like, and add the background color at the top of the inner line.
Now create an Overlock bridge,
add the outline of the eyebrow film and inner line at the same time.
Adjust various properties and color.
Let's proceed with the presentation of the overall shape of the eyebrow.
Drawing the shape of the eyebrow.
My card is the outline of the eyebrow.
I draw a line above the eyebrow.
I click on the Lana of the eyebrow.
For the skin of the face, I will use Substance's Flecked Tartan fabric.
You can find it in the Substance folder in the Library window.
Drag it to the fabric type of the face panel, and you can replace the original fabric texture.
After selecting this fabric type, you can modify some of the properties of Substance in the property editor.
I made the bones of the body in Maya, tied the bones and made the animation.
In order to be closer to the structure of the dragon in the real world, I used round pieces as the bones.
The body structure of the dragon also has a similar support structure.
There will be a stick at the bottom of the support structure, and the performer will perform the dragon's dance by controlling the stick.
The animation will be exported in the Alembic cache format and used in Marvelous Designer.
Enter the Alembic file, and we can see the animation in the animation editor at the bottom.
Create a round sheet according to the size made in Maya.
Stick each round sheet on the round sheet and repeat the steps.
All round sheets are placed in the 3D window, and then switch to the Stabilizer tool.
Add a Stabilizer to the top of the grid on the double sheet outline.
Right-click on any Stabilizer and select Stabilize all Stabilizers on the virtual model.
This way, the sheet will move along the round sheet.
Then create a rectangular sheet with the round sheet as the width value.
The height is 1000 mm, because the diameter between each round sheet I set in Maya is 1000 mm.
For arranging these sheets, we will create an arrangement point and arrangement board to make it more convenient.
Go to the main menu, virtual model, virtual model editor.
Add an arrangement board under the arrangement label bar.
Place it between the two round sheets and rotate it.
Increase the height of X and Y.
Then add an arrangement point and set it to the arrangement board just created.
Open the display arrangement point, select the rectangular sheet, click on the arrangement point to arrange the sheet.
Created the marking line between the wheel plates
Pre 그리고创建好板面之间的缝纫线
Examine the material by changing to Nylon Canvas and opening the simulation.
gi81 Jewish
Copy and paste the body version to repeat the previous operation.
After the model is finished, I will use the animation editor to record the transformation process of the five dragons.
Before recording, please make sure that all the fixed needles are fixed to the virtual model.
Change the simulation attribute to animation, then go to the attribute editor, turn off the conflict on the ground, and set the gravity to 0.
Set the air resistance to 3, the scene time change to 2 to get a more stable simulation effect.
After adjustment, click the record button to wait.
Now, Marvelous Designer will record the animation for you.
Now please check the final effect.
After the action is modified, you can export the file for subsequent adjustment and rendering.
Before recording, we will find out the translation method of the像
Please help us like and subscribe to our channel them今日は
The trial and Protect Manga of the time ingame
Therefore, please immediately come to our channel.
Thank you for watching while recording.
Take care of yourselves everyone.
Goodbye everyone.
Bye bye for now!